Finding Aid for the S. Charles Lee papers LSC.1384
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Photographs
  - Public/Institutional
    - Aero Services [Palmdale Airport] - Palmdale, Elevation rendering (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Arcadia City Hall - Arcadia. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Armory. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Bomb Shelter / Pedestrian Tunnel. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Emergency Unit. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Fifty-Ninth Street School - Los Angeles, Exterior view (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Fire Station. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Franks (A.J.) Mausoleum. - Chicago, 1932; Perspective sketch (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Franks (A.J.) Mausoleum. - Chicago, 1932; Exterior view (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Franks (A.J.) Mausoleum. - Chicago, 1932; Crypt (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Greek Orthodox Church - Los Angeles. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Hospital - Newman. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles County Courthouse - Compton. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Mary Pickford Building Home for the Aged., 1946.; Perspective rendering (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Mount Sinai Hospital/Clinic. - Los Angeles, 1930s?; Perspective rendering-Clinic (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Mount Sinai Hospital/Clinic. - Los Angeles, 1930s?; Perspective rendering-Hospital (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Pershing Square Garage - Los Angeles, Perspective sketch (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Pershing Square Garage - Los Angeles, Perspective sketch, c. 1930 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Temple Israel. - Hollywood, 1948; Lee at construction site (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Temple Israel. - Hollywood, 1948; Auditorium, rear (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Temple Israel. - Hollywood, 1948; Auditorium, front (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Temple Israel. - Hollywood, 1948; Entrance (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Temple Israel. - Hollywood, 1948; Exterior (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Temple Israel. - Hollywood, 1948; Interior, rendering (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Temple Israel. - Hollywood, 1948; Interior, rendering (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Woodbury College - Los Angeles. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Temple Israel. - Hollywood., 1948 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Variety Club (Premature Clinic) - Los Angeles. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Westwood Temple. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Development Projects
    - Barrington Westgate Acres. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Century Industrial Corporation. - Los Angeles, 1950; Perspective rendering; Los Angeles Airport Industrial Tract Hayden-Lee construction site office (Box 12, Folder 20)
      Lee's office at the Los Angeles Airport Industrial Tract
    - Los Feliz Apartments, Construction photos. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Maclay Rancho, Open land site photos. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Bedford. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Gilmore Village [Parkinson ' Parkinson]. (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Civil Air Patrol. (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Earthquakes. (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Letters/Correspondence. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous 1, Walter Kumme, Mural Paintings. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous 2. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous 3. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Personal, Lee in bathing suit (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal, Lee portrait (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal, Lee portrait (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal., 1936.; Lee caricature (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal, Lee at desk (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal. - Oceanside, 1948; Lee with camera (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal. - Oceanside, 1948; Lee with airplane Oceanside (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal, Lee with airplane (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal, Lee in uniform (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal - Los Angeles, Lee at office door, 1648 Wilshire (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal, Lee on hunting trip (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Personal., 1949.; Lee with Councilman Davis (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Playad. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Popcorn machine/Candy counter. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Fair., 1939. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Renderings
    - Wasco Theatre - Wasco. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Apartments [French] - concept, Perspective sketch (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apartments [Deco] - concept, Perspective sketch (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apartments Bruce Arms - Los Angeles, Exterior, 532 S. Hobart, Los Angeles (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apartments, Exterior (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apartments [Moderne]. - concept, 1938; Perspective sketch (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Associates Incorporated Apartment - Beverly Hills. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Associates Incorporated Residence - Burbank. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Boasberg House - Westwood, Exterior (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Boasberg House - Westwood, Living room (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Boasberg House - Westwood, Bedroom (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Boasberg House - Westwood, Stairway (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Tod Browning, Beverly Hills. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - El Mirador Apartments [California Builders] - Hollywood, Entry (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - El Mirador Apartments [California Builders] - Hollywood, Setting (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - El Mirador Apartments [California Builders] - Hollywood, Exterior (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Cohen House [M.M. Cohen] - Los Angeles, Facade (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Cohen House [M.M. Cohen] - Los Angeles, Entry close-up (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Cummings House, Exterior view (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Davis Residence - Monrovia. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Deutch Residence. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Eudemiller Residence. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Sun room (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Exterior front (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Exterior side elevation (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Dining room (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Living room (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Bedroom (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Goldsmith House [J. Goldsmith] - Los Angeles, Kitchen (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Houses. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hungerford (Leo) Residence - Los Angeles. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Hunt (Phillip) Residence. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Jacob Kalb (Du Barry) Apartment. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - King. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Kornhandler. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Perspective sketch (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Community room (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Apt interior, bedroom (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Apt interior, dining room (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Lobby desk (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Writing room (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Lobby (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Exterior view (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925; Courtyard, fountain (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Dining room (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Living room (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Entrance elevation, sketch (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Exterior view, garden elev. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Exterior view, entrance (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Oldknow (Oscar) House. - Bel Air, 1936; Living room (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Pacht (Isaac) Residence - Los Feliz?. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Camrose Apartments (Phillips) - Hollywood. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Dining room (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Entry (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Kitchen (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Bathroom (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Built-in radio-phonograph? (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Fireplace (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Dining room (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Concealed bar, opened (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Living room (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sheehan (Howard) Apartment [Fox Wilshire Theatre Penthouse] - Beverly Hills, Bedroom (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sherman (J.W.) Residence - Los Angeles. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Silbert (Bruce Arms) Apartment. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Simon Residence - Beverly Hills. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Troyer Brothers apartment. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Universal Holding Company (Lexington Manor Apartments). (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Universal Holding Company duplexes - Los Angeles. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925-26; Principal elevation, on linen (Box 172)
    - Haddon Hall [Oberndorf Apartments]. - Los Angeles, 1925-26; Detail, elevator door frame (Box 172)
- Surveys
  - Aller, March 10, 1935. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Associates Incorporated., August 1936, May 23, 1946. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Bailey, W.J. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Barancik, B.., June 1926. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bearman, William B.., November 1928. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Bershon, D.., September 20, 1940, March 14, 1941. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Blink., February 1946. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Blumfield, Henry., November 1940. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Boasberg, Albert., January 1934. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Booth, Walter., March 24, 1931. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Browning, Tod., September 1926. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Broxton / Weyburn. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Bryant Acres., March 9, 1926. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Calco. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Caldwell., August 14, 1936. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - California Realty Company., July 1930. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Camrose Apartments., October 1934. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Cedar Lane. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Century Industrial., 1948. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Chalon Road., April 30, 1931. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Cohen., December 8, 1938. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cohen, M.M.., August 1926. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Collier Street., November 10, 1948. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Comida Way. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Compton. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Conrad, L.., December 1925. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Copeland, J.I.., September 1935. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Crane., December 1925. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Cummings, Irving., February 1925. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Danziger., November 1926. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Davis, Charles., November 1924. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Deutch., May 1925. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Dick, Robert., January 1926. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Dodge, Mrs. J.., October 1939. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - East Side Auditorium., December 10, 1928. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Ellwood, Maren., January 21, 1947. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Feldman, Philip., November 1927. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Ferguson, Joe., April 1929. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - First Baptist Church., June 14, 1935. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Fiske, R.W.., April 1924. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Foothill Boulevard., January 13, 1928. (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Fox Deluxe., February 6, 1936. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Fox West Coast., October 1929, August 21, 1930, April 1931, June 6, 1935, November 19, 1940, August 24, 1941. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Franklin / Argyle., October 1930. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Friedman, Ad., February 1925. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Gentry Theatre., July 27, 1937. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Glass, Samuel., February 1925. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Goldenberg., June 14, 1935. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Goldsmith, Laurence H.., December 2, 1938. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Goldsmith., March 3, 1924 - April 1925. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Goodman, Al., July 25, 1935. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Greek Church., May 13, 1938. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Greene ' Hinkle., December 20, 1945. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Gumbiner, H.L.., February 1929. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Hanson, Albert., February 1937. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Harowitz, Harry., March 1925. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Harrison., February 1924. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Harrison ' Rapp., August 1920. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Harrison, Guy., November 1924. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Hathaway, Charles., July 1926. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Hitchings, T.C.., November 1924, January 1925. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Hollywood / Hudson. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Holm, Don Lee Company., January 1925. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Hungerford, Leo., March 11, 1935. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hunt, P.., April 1925, May 1927, November 1930. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Huntington Drive. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - International Investment Company., January 1929. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Jacobs. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Janss Investment Company. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Jones, Burton I. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Kaplan Turner Cohen., August 5, 1938. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Kaplan, M.L.., January 1929. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Kass ' Ruben. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - La Tijera Theatre., July-September 1947. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Landeau., March 29, 1938. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Lanitt., December 1924. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lazarus, Simon M.., 1944. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lee, S. Charles., September 1925, January 1927, September 1927, May 12, 1933, May 7, 1935. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Levy, Mrs.., March 1931. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Long Beach Boulevard. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Los Feliz Blvd.., April 15, 1936. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Lyons, Charles., April 1932. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Macko, William., August 31, 1945. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Malsman., September 1929. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Manchester. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Mann., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Maple. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Market Street., March 1937. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Mayer, Louis B.., December 1927. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - McGhee., April 1925. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Mellos, Athanasios K.., October-December 1945. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Meyer, F.W. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Midvale Avenue. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Modine, E.E.., January 1925. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Newman. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Norton Brothers ' Morris., June 22, 1933. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Oberndorf Brothers., July 1925. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Pacht, Isaac., January 1927, February 1927. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Pacific Amusement., May 1929, September 1929. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Peabody ' Company., November 21, 1947. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Picwood Theatre., February 26, 1937. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Piltzer, D.., November 1936. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Porto Marina Way., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rector., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Redondo., July 1935. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Redwood City Theatres, August 22, 1930. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Robinson, Louis., December 14, 1945. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, S.A. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Rosenberg., May 1924. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Rusinow, Sydney., November 17, 1945. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - San Diego Housing., February 25, 1942. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - San Diego Theatre Corporation., August 19, 1939. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - San Luis Obispo Theatres., March 1941. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - San Pablo Rancho., September 1, 1941. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Santa Clara Avenue., February 6, 1936. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Scheinman., August 4, 1933. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Scheinman, Arthur., April 19, 1926. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Seligman., February 1947. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Senator Theatre., July 7, 1925. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Shepler., January 1928. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Sherman, J.W.., January 1925. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Shidler., July 1919. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Shirley Corporation., April 1, 1940. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Silbert., May 21, 1923, April 14, 1925. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Simmonds., July 24, 1936. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Sims, Herman., December 2, 1944. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Small, E.D.., March 1927. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Babe., August 16, 1927. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Standard Trailer Park. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Temple City Theatre., February 22, 1940. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Terman, S.E.., September 1945. (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Thompson, Earle., January 22, 1941. (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Tower Bowl., November 30, 1940. (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Trabue Pittman., July 1930. (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Troyer Brothers., February 12, 1925, December 1925, October 1926. (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Ullman, Frank., August 2, 1941. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Universal Holding Company., January 1927. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Variety Club., February 21, 1944. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Venice Brush Company., November 6, 1946. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Washaver, D.., November 2, 1928. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Washington Street / Spruce Street., January 7, 1936. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Waverly Drive., April 1936. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Weisman, S.M.., November 14, 1928, March 1929, January 28, 1935. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Westgate Acres, August 1949. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Whitson, Lewis ' Schank., March 24, 1939. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Wickman, Emil., July 23, 1936. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Williams, L.J.., November 4, 1938. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Wilshire / San Vicente., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Wilshire Boulevard., March 1936. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Windsor Hills., July 25, 1941. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Wometco Theatres., August 1927. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Woodruff, W.N.., May 23, 1935. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Zimmerman., March 16, 1940. (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Negatives
  - Negatives - Theatres, duplicates - 1.1 (Academy) - 2.13 Fox Phoenix. (Box 22)
  - Negatives, Theatres - 2.15 (Fox Bakersfield) - 4.7 (Mexico). (Box 23)
  - Negatives - Theatres - 5.1 (Misc.) - 7.4 (Tujunga). (Box 24)
  - Negatives - 7.5 (Tumbleweed) - 7.11 (Vogue Southgate). (Box 25)
  - Negatives - Residential duplicates - 8.1 (Apts.) - 9.5 (Simon). (Box 26)
  - Negatives - Commercial - 9.10 (Airplane Club) - 10.7 (Lee Office Building). (Box 27)
  - Negatives - Public / Developments / Misc. - 12.2 (Arcadia City Hall) - 13.4 (Playad) (Box 28)
- Blueprints/Rolled Plans
  - A ' A Diecasting, corner Westwood(?) ' El Segundo, A-13. (Box 101)
  - AB Sign, 5438 W. 104th, 6-A. (Box 102)
  - Azusa Housing. (Box 48)
  - Berkoff, Louis - Medical Office Building, Los Angeles. (Box 34, 47, 66, 75)
  - Bliss-craft. (Box 121)
  - Bliss-Craft, 13007 S. Western Ave. (Box 116)
  - Bliss-craft, Building 112. (Box 122)
  - Bonner, 5285 W. 102nd, B-8. (Box 104)
  - Building 107, 5305 W. 102nd, B-5. (Box 106)
  - Cal Video Tube, 5232 W. 104th, 9-A. (Box 84)
  - Carlos Theatre, Redondo Theatre, Alexander, Globe, Mt. Helena (?), Earl, 1 roll - tissues taped onto Kraft paper; colored renderings. (Box 130)
  - Chapultepec Theatre, Mexico City, 1 roll blue lines - plans. (Box 77)
  - Charlton, 5451 W. 104th, B-2. (Box 110)
  - Class A Theatre for Gumbiner Theatrical Enterprises, (Los Angeles?), 1 roll - sheets are details. (Box 132)
  - Class A Theatre, Gumbiner, 615 S. Broadway, C-2. (Box 134)
  - Creative Process, Building 106, Western Ave., B-6. (Box 107)
  - Creative Process, Western Ave. (Box 85)
  - Delmar Bowling Alley (for Jack White) Blue Line., 1958 (Box 61)
  - Edificion para Inversiones Estrella, South America - blue line factory building - Colon., 1962. (Box 49)
  - Electronics industries, Manchester ' Hindry, 10-A. (Box 91)
  - Floodlite Service, Incorporated, Julia B. Sale, Los Angeles. (Box 54)
  - Fox Wilshire Theatre (Pacific Amusement), 1930, 1 roll b.p. - details, other could not unroll. (Box 133)
  - Fox Wilshire Theatre (Pacific Amusement), Beverly HIlls. (Box 37)
  - Fox Wilshire Theatre (Pacific Amusement), Beverly Hills. (Box 76)
  - Fox Wilshire Theatre (Pacific Amusement), Beverly Hills. (Box 140)
  - Harn, 13401 S. Western Ave., M-3. (Box 112)
  - Harn, 8561 Warner Drive, A-11. (Box 92)
  - Harn, office copy. (Box 113)
  - Harper Theatre (Glen Harper), Fontana. (Box 71)
  - Harper Theatre (Glen Harper), Fontana. (Box 222)
  - Hayden Lee (Building 110). (Box 40)
  - Hayden Lee Corporation factory for Blisscraft of Hollywood (Building 112), Gardena. (Box 56)
  - Hayden Lee Corporation factory for Lee Tex Rubber Plant, Los Angeles. (Box 32, 42, 48, 55, 58, 63)
  - Hayden Lee factory for Hollypark - Crenshaw Company. (Box 39)
  - Hayden Lee factory for Hollypark - Crenshaw Company. (Box 41)
  - Hayden Lee factory for Hollypark - Crenshaw Company. (Box 44)
  - Hayden Lee factory for Hollypark - Crenshaw Company. (Box 57)
  - Hollywood - Western Building, Mayer Investment Company, Hollywood, Blueprints - used in construction - (fragile). (Box 80)
  - Hollywood - Western Building, Mayer Investment Company, Hollywood, construction blueprints - fragile. (Box 81)
  - Hollywood - Western Building, Mayer Investment Company, Hollywood, F.S.D.'s - on trace - some prints - fragile. (Box 83)
  - Hollywood - Western Building, Mayer Investment Company, Hollywood. (Box 129)
  - Hollywood Silk, 5450 W. 104th, 4-A. (Box 98)
  - Hughes Air Craft, 59N, 5340 104th, 3-A. (Box 103)
  - Inyokern Project. (Box 53)
  - Inyokern Project. (Box 59)
  - Job no.607, 529, 664, 666, 529, 540, 582, 583, 561, 619, 593, 588. (Box 130)
  - Job no.630, 677, 721, 821, 561, 610, 751. (Box 130)
  - Kaplan ' Greenburg Fourplex, Los Angeles. (Box 69)
  - Kay Electric, 5441 W. 104, 6-A. (Box 95)
  - Kay Electric, 5441 W. 104th, 5-A. (Box 100)
  - Kleger, 5325 W. 102nd, A-12. (Box 93)
  - Los Angeles County Courthouse, Compton. (Box 46)
  - Los Angeles County Courthouse, Compton. (Box 65)
  - Los Angeles County Courthouse, Compton. (Box 68)
  - Los Angeles County Courthouse, Compton., 1952. (Box 204)
  - Los Angeles Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles. (Box 82)
  - Los Angeles Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles. (Box 136)
  - Los Angeles Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), 615 S. Broadway. (Box 135)
  - Los Angeles Theatre, Class A, Theatre, Gumbiner, 615 S. Broadway. (Box 137)
  - Los Angeles Theatre, Class A. Theatre, Gumbiner, 615 S. Broadway. (Box 138)
  - Los Prados Apartments, San Mateo. (Box 30)
  - Mar Vista Engineering. (Box 126)
  - Mar Vista Engineering. (Box 127)
  - Model Die Casting no.19. (Box 88)
  - Modern Plating, 5400 W. 104th, 1-B. (Box 111)
  - Picwood Theatre (Earl Collins), Los Angeles. (Box 73)
  - Picwood Theatre (Earl Collins), Los Angeles, Large roll, colored renderings on trace taped to Kraft paper. (Box 130)
  - Picwood Theatre, 1946 (Pico ' Westwood), Arch. and mech. On trace - fragile. (Box 86)
  - Picwood Theatre, Egyptian Theatre, La Tijera, large roll - colored renderings on trace taped to Kraft paper. (Box 130)
  - Picwood., 1947. (Box 114)
  - Plastic Process no.1. (Box 87)
  - Precision Sheet Metal. (Box 123)
  - Precision Sheet Metal, no.22, 1-C. (Box 118)
  - Precision Sheet Metal, no.22, 1-C. (Box 124)
  - Precision Sheet Metal, 30B. (Box 125)
  - Republic Heater, 10200 Aviation, B-8. (Box 109)
  - Reseda Theatre (Charles Grenzbach), Reseda. (Box 45)
  - Sanford Jewelry, 5242 W. 104th 2-A. (Box 90)
  - SCK Corporation. Steel Sign. (Box 60)
  - Sherman Oaks Market, corner Cedros ' Ventura, B-7. (Box 105)
  - Sunshine Building, 102A, Western Ave., 15-A. (Box 96)
  - Sunshine Building, 102A, Western Ave., 16-A. (Box 99)
  - Tower Bowl, A. Hanson, San Diego. (Box 74)
  - Tower Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles, 4 blueprints - electric plan. (Box 29)
  - Tower Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles. (Box 36)